const store = {
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where you grab your heelside edge (between your feet) with your front hand',
        answers: [
          'Mindy',
          'Crail',
          'Melon',
          'Indy'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Melon'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the jib trick where you pop the tail of your board up and over the feature, landing perpendicular in a sliding position',
        answers: [
          'Michael Jackson',
          'Boardslide',
          'Noseslide',
          'Lipslide'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Lipslide'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where you grab your heelside edge (between your feet) with your rear hand',
        answers: [
          'Stalefish',
          'Mute',
          'Japan',
          'Chicken Salad'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Stalefish'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the jib trick where you jump all the way across the feature, landing perpendicular on just the tail of your board',
        answers: [
          'Boardslide',
          'Hardway',
          'Bluntslide',
          'Lipslide'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Bluntslide'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where you reach between your feet with your back hand, through your legs and grab the heel edge of your snowboard',
        answers: [
          'Canadian Bacon',
          'Shifty',
          'Method',
          'Roast Beef'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Roast Beef'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the jib trick where you pop off a board or lipslide, spinning 270 in the opposite direction you jumped on',
        answers: [
          'Knuckle',
          'Pretzel',
          'Hardway',
          'Rewind'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Pretzel'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where your rear hand grabs your toe edge slightly inside your rear foot',
        answers: [
          'Indy',
          'Nosegrab',
          'Mute',
          'Tindy'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Indy'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the jib trick where you slide straight down the feature, nose first, with weight evenly on both feet',
        answers: [
          'Slide',
          'Boardslide',
          '50-50',
          'Press'
        ],
        correctAnswer: '50-50'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where you grab the toe edge (preferably in-between the binding) with your front hand and tweak it out behind your back',
        answers: [
          'Japan',
          'Alley-oop',
          'Seatbelt',
          'Rodeo'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Japan'
      },
      {
        question: 'Name the grab where both of your hands grab the nose, while the rear leg is boned and the front leg is pulled up',
        answers: [
          'Taipan',
          'Cross Rocket',
          'Cork',
          'Rocket Air'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 'Rocket Air'
      },
    ],
    quizStarted: false,
    questionNumber: 0,
    score: 0
  };
  

